[
{
"id":"1",
"question":"At a conference, 12 members shook hands with each other before & after the meeting. How many total number of hand shakes occurred?",
"answer":"132",
"opt1":"100",
"opt2":"132",
"opt3":"144",
"opt4":"121"
},
{
"id":"2",
"question":"The day after the day after tomorrow is four days before Monday. What day is it today?",
"answer":"Monday",
"opt1":"Monday",
"opt2":"Tuesday",
"opt3":"Wednesday",
"opt4":"Friday"
},
{
"id":"3",
"question":"In the above problem, E is lighter in weight than which of the following pairs?",
"answer":"A,B",
"opt1":"D,C",
"opt2":"B,D",
"opt3":"A,D",
"opt4":"A,B"
},
{
"id":"4",
"question":"6121135 is to flame as 21215120 is to ?",
"answer":"bloat",
"opt1":"bloat",
"opt2":"voice",
"opt3":"castle",
"opt4":"bald"
},
{
"id":"5",
"question":"Forest is to tree as tree is to ?",
"answer":"leaf",
"opt1":"plant",
"opt2":"leaf",
"opt3":"branch",
"opt4":"mangrove"
},
{
"id":"6",
"question":"29, 27, 24, 20, 15… What is next?",
"answer":"9",
"opt1":"10",
"opt2":"11",
"opt3":"7",
"opt4":"9"
},
{
"id":"7",
"question":"Which one of the five choices makes the best comparison? PEACH is to HCAEP as 46251 is to:",
"answer":"15264",
"opt1":"51462",
"opt2":"12654",
"opt3":"15264",
"opt4":"26541"
},
{
"id":"8",
"question":"5, 10, 19, 32, 49, 70… What is next?",
"answer":"95",
"opt1":"100",
"opt2":"121",
"opt3":"95",
"opt4":"99"
},
{
"id":"9",
"question":"Which one of the numbers does not belong in the following series? 2 – 3 – 6 – 7 – 8 – 14 – 15 – 30",
"answer":"8",
"opt1":"30",
"opt2":"15",
"opt3":"8",
"opt4":"7"
},
{
"id":"10",
"question":"If you rearrange the letter “CIFAIPC” you would have the name of a(n):",
"answer":"Ocean",
"opt1":"City",
"opt2":"Animal",
"opt3":"River",
"opt4":"Ocean"
}
]